Neighbors, Inc. 110 110
Stage
- Series 1
  - Police Community relations, Undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Protest groups, Undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Race Relations Reporter, Undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Resources, Undated (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Takoma PTA newsletters, Undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Films and Bibliography, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Neighbors' Maps, Undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Free-D.C., Undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs Association, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Home Rule for D.C. Articles, corresp. from Fauntroy, etc., Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Human relation news Chicago, Undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Health Education and Welfare Dept., U.S. Govt., Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Misc., Board Business, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Neighbors' Ink, Corresp., Undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Neighbors, Inc. Legislation Committee, Undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - New Directions for Neighbors, May 10 1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Statement House Judiciary Committee - HJR #396 Home Rule, 24672 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Statement To Senate Subcommittee on D.C. Appropriations on FY 1968 Budget, Undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Public Works Statement, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Statement on D.C. representation (Sen. Judiciary Subcommittee), 24785 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Statement to D.C. Board of Educ., Undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Statement of NI to the National Commission on Urban problems, 24773 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Statement on elected school board (Sen. Cmte. D.C. Affairs), 24804 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Statement of Neighbors re the 1962 D.C. Budget before the Board of Comm., Oct 1960 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - NI endorses City Council Candidates, 24704 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Violation Complaint forms, Undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Board Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Executive Dtr. corresp., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - IUD challenge, back issues, Undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Jewish Foundation for retarded Children, Undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - The Lisle Fellowship, Inc., Undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - League of Women Voters, Undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Crime stats. - Studies, Undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Day Care information, Undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - President of the U.S., Undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Panels on "Churches, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Dept. Highway and Traffic Action Plan, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - D.C. Civic Assoc., Undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - D.C. Democratic Economics, Undated (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - D.C. PIRG and Public Citizen, Undated (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Bureau of Social Science research, Undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - ACLU, Undated (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Newsletter, Undated (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Business groups, Undated (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Capital improvements budget, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Census date, stat. info., Undated (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Church literature, Undated (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Center for a Voluntary Society, Undated (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Project Kindle materials 'work papers', Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Extra copies of Newsletters, 1969-1975, 1977-1980, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - AandB Festival, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1974-1976, 1978, 1981-1983, 1986-1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1958-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)